with the MVP the best advice is to
actually
launch something quickly
and iterate get a product into the hands
of your customers
and then learn whether it helps them or
doesn't and then iterate it and prove it
over time the wrong answer is to do 100
surveys and 600 user interviews and
contact every single one of the
competitors and spend you know a year
fundraising and hire 100 people and you
know all these other things that you can
distract yourself with that it might
appear like are the smart things
but in reality they really don't
highlight the most important point about
an MVP which is you'd only really start
learning about your user when you put a
product in front of it